(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-10T16:33:57.743370",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
教えて 教えてよ その仕組みを
Tell me, tell me how this works...
僕の中に 誰がいるの？
...who is inside of me?
壊れた 壊れたよ この世界で
I'm broken, broken in this world,
君が笑う 何も見えずに
where you're smiling, seeing nothing at all.
壊れた僕なんてさ 息を止め
A broken me like this... stopping my breath,
ほどけない もう ほどけないよ 真実さえ freeze
unraveling, unravelling... even truth—freeze.
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない
Can I break it? Can't break it? Go mad or not?
あなたを見つけて 揺れた
Finding you, I started to shake.
歪んだ世界にだんだん 僕は透き通って見えなくなって
In this twisted world, I gradually grow transparent and vanish.
見ないでで 僕のことを 見つめないで
Don't look at me... please don't look at me.
誰かが描いた世界の中で あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
In a world someone painted, I don't want to hurt you.
覚えていて 僕のことを 鮮やかなまま
Remember me... as vivid as I used to be.
無限に広がる孤独が絡まる 無邪気に笑った記憶が刺さって
Endless solitude entwines, innocent memories pierce me.
動けない 動けない… unravelling the world
Can't move, can't move... unravelling the world.
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
It changed... I couldn't change it back.
2つが絡まる 2人が滅びる
Two things entwine, two people perish.
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない
Can break, can't break, go mad, can't go mad.
あなたを汚さないよ 揺れた
I won't defile you... I shook.
教えて 教えてよ
Tell me, tell me,
その仕組みを 僕の中に誰がいるの?
how this works, who is inside me?
壊れた 壊れたよ この世界で
Broken, broken in this world,
君が笑う 何も見えずに
you laugh, seeing nothing at all.
壊れた僕なんてさ 息を止め
I, who am broken, hold my breath,
ほどけない もう ほどけないよ 真実さえ freeze
can't unravel anymore, even truth, freeze.
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない
Can break, can't break, go mad, can't go mad,
あなたを見つけて 揺るんだ
finding you, swaying.
歪んだ世界にだんだん 僕は透き通って見えなくなって
In the distorting world, I become transparent and disappear.
見つけないで 僕のことを 見つめないで
Don't find me, don't look at me.
誰かが描いた世界の中で あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
In a world someone painted, I don't want to hurt you.
覚えているよ 僕のことを
Remember me,
鮮やかなままで
vivid as ever.
無限に広がる孤独が絡まる 無邪気に笑った記憶が刺さって
Infinite loneliness entwines, innocent laughing memories pierce.
動けない 動けない
Can't move, can't move,
動けない 動けないよ
can't move, can't move.
unravelling the world
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
It changed, couldn't change,
2つが絡まる 2人が滅びる
two entwined, two perish.
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない
Can break, can't break, go mad, can't go mad,
あなたを汚さないよ
I won't defile you.
歪んだ世界にだんだん 僕は透き通って見えなくなって
In the distorting world, I become transparent and disappear.
見つけないで 僕のことを 見つめないで
Don't find me, don't look at me.
誰かが仕組んだ孤独な罠に 未来がほぐれてしまう前に
In the lonely trap someone set, before the future unravels.
思い出して 僕のことを
Remember me,
鮮やかなままで
vivid as ever.
忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで
Don't forget, don't forget, don't forget, don't forget.
変わってしまったことに paralyze
Paralyzed by the changes,
変えられないことだらけの paradise
in a paradise of unchangeable things.
覚えているよ 僕のことを
Remember me.
教えて 教えて ぼくの中に誰がいるの?
Tell me, tell me, is someone inside me?
みなさん!
Minassan!
Hey everybody, it's me, Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth, everybody's favorite hard-working Shinigami!
Back in action today with a brand new show for all of you guys that I've been working super super hard for.
I hope you guys are as excited as I am.
This is my official, officially, officially my second birthday live, official 3D, 3D live show.
I hope you guys are super super hyped for it because, oh man, there's so much good stuff!
I hope you guys are super-duper hyped for it because, oh man, there's so much good stuff!
I can't wait to show you, but there's a special rule for today's, for today's live.
And that rule is no down time, which means... which means, I mean there's no downtime.
And that rule is 'No Downtime', which means... which means, I mean, there's no downtime.
There's, there's no slow anything, no slow songs, no slow MCs, no slow Mori.
100% Hajimete no Chu zemi-taina kanji, going real crazy, that's why you gotta use the hashtag hashtag No Downtime and post a bunch of screenshots!
100% 'Hajimete no Chuu' zemi-like feeling, going real crazy, that's why you gotta use the hashtag #NoDowntime and post a bunch of screenshots!
Can you do that? A bunch of screenshots and your thoughts, screenshots and your thoughts about this show.
And I'd be really really happy if you did that, because we got a lot of great guests, we got a lot of great performances, and not to mention we have a great stage!
Would you like to take a look at the stage with me? Take a look at the Underdome, under underworld dome? I haven't come up with a name for it yet, but isn't it great?
It's a special secret place that I found in the underworld, where the moon sometimes comes down on the fourth of April, which happens to be my birthday.
So I figured that it would be the perfect setting for all of us to have a great show together.
I invited a bunch of my friends, and it's gonna be amazing! There's a lot of great surprises ahead.
Additionally, um... I can see a bunch of you in the crowd. I know you're cheering for me. Hey, what's up skeletons?
Except you look a little more human-shaped, congratulations on that, but I'm looking forward to doing my best for you guys.
And as a matter of fact...
you guys should definitely stream and listen to a lot if you haven't had time
and check out the MV because the art is amazing.
That song is called Overkill. Check it out.
テメェの所為です
It's all your fault.
どの子が好き？？
Which girl do you like??
この子に決めた
I chose this one.
角度を調節
Adjusting the angle,
覚悟微調節
fine-tuning resolve.
飽きたらポイから
Once I'm bored I toss 'em, so
Place any bets, decide who is special and discard the rest
Gambler by nature, chips start to stack
Racing lovely animals until they crack
やいのやいの
Fussing and whining,
張り付け parasite
nailed-down parasite,
ヤンデレッテル
yandere label—
テメェの所為です
it's all your fault.
Black out, break down
toss it when you've had enough
やっちゃえいっちゃえ
Go ahead and snap!
I can tell you're not impressed
右向け右 左向け左
Face right, face left,
leave the defective, unworthy of investment
飽きたらポイから
Once I'm bored I toss 'em, so
hot mess, worthless doll
よってたかっていらっしゃい
come gather around all together!
Gambler by nature, chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
Beautiful dreams await modest hearts
close your eyes and all you'll see is black
才能サイコパスと紙一重 やっちまったの後悔で fever
Genius and psychopath are a hair apart, fever of regret
もういい！
enough already!
starving !
時間の無駄無駄 やっちゃえいっちゃえ
Waste of time, just go for it!
I can tell you're not impressed
えぐればほぐす つらら咲く血だらけ
Gouging and loosening, icicles blooming in blood
どうにかなりそう どうにでもなりそう
Seems like it'll work out, somehow it'll work out
ぶっとい絆
thick bonds,
lonely lonely trouble in paradise
oh if only 愛を讃えて「あいうえお」から「ん」まで昇って見下してやるわ
oh, if only, praising love, rising from "A" to "N" to look down on you!
テメェの所為です
It's all your fault.
貼り付け parasite
Nailed-down parasite,
ヤンデレッテル
yandere label—
テメェの所為です
it's all your fault.
Black out, break down
toss it when you're out of love
やっちゃえいっちゃえ
Go ahead and snap!
I'm the one that's not impressed
テメェの所為です 責任とはなれ パッと光って 華ひらくわ
It's all your fault, becoming responsibility, shining bright and blooming into flowers!
パッと光って 華ひらくわ
Shining bright and blooming into flowers!
detonator will come out of nowhere yeah
trick, cheat, fraud, lie, sulfur in the air
so let it be, oh let it be, says all debaters
six times knocking on the door
no response, but hey you already
back to back!
death comes riding on a midnight train
conscience is screaming to the end
back to back!
can not let anyone do it again
i can no longer pretend
give me a break , you damned
Give me a break, you damned
just wanna get back my dice again
blazing down , what a heavy day
Blazing down, what a heavy day
now , you hear the rumble from the ground
Now, you hear the rumble from the ground
Now, you hear the rumble from the ground, yeah
Trick,
Cheat,
Fraud,
Lie,
Clown is dancing around, yeah
“So let it be, oh let it be”
"So let it be, oh let it be,"
seems i’m the traitor
seems I'm the traitor.
Six times knockin' on the door,
One last chance, you've gotta stand
Back to back! Death comes arrivin' on a midnight train!
Back to back! Conscience is screamin' to the end!
Back to back! Cannot let anyone do it again!
Back to back! I can no longer pretend!
Give me a break, you damned!
Just wanna get back my dice again,
Blazing down! What a heavy day!
Hey! Hey! Hey! All right!
We made a contract with a clown and had a high old time...
nobody doubted his true purpose, oh yeah!
Not knowing we had given up everything we had left,
all odds and options denied, trapped here in this dead end...
Back to back! Death comes arrivin' on a midnight train!
Back to back! Conscience is screamin' to the end!
Back to back! Blade is already on your jugular vein!
Back to back! It's now or never! Last chance... to stand!
Give me a break, you damned!
Just wanna get back my dice again,
Blazing down! What a heavy day!
Ina, Ina, Ina...
Thank you so much for coming and singing Heavy Day together with me at Taals! It was so fun!
Aali, happy birthday!
Thank you for inviting me today! This stage looks great!
Those pillars of fire are hot though!
Yeah, that's right. You know they're hot, just like our intense GG vibes and our synergy.
This is... this is maybe... I don't know, I think that we've... you've been at almost every single one of my birthday lives, and so I just want to say sincerely, thank you from the bottom of my heart, Ninomae Ina'nis.
Keep it up and good luck with the rest of the show!
Bye-bye! Wishing you all the best!
Bye-bye, Ina! Thank you so much for coming!
Well, we have a bunch more guests that are coming, but I can't allow myself to rest for even a moment because, you guys, the theme is #NoDowntime.
So I'm just going to be here jogging in place... If I allow myself to rest, then it's false advertising! Right, Deadbeats? That's what that is, false advertising!
So let's go! Keep it moving, keep it moving! No breaks, no breaks, no breaks, no breaks on the Mori!
On to the next! What could it be? What could it be?
圧倒的に多数の人が
An overwhelming majority of people
無闇矢鱈と囃し立ててるよ 結局誰が悪いのかなんて
blindly egging others on. Who's really to blame here anyway?
知る由も無いぜ 味方無し 人の背に立つ背に立つ あなたの目の前の目の前が嫌い
There's no way of knowing, with no allies. Standing behind people, hating the very face right before your eyes.
またアンチで呟く日が満ちりゃ 勝っても負けても痛み無し
Twitter haters mutter again as days pass; win or lose, there's no pain.
愛憎歪みが立ち、そりゃ勝っても負けても痛み無し愛
Love and hatred distortion rises; win or lose, there's no pain.
何も作れないまま 何も得られないままで
Leaving nothing created, leaving nothing gained,
さあ何度も繰り返せ
come on, repeat it over and over again!
現実は何処へ 探して
Where is the truth? Seek it out
Where's my soul?
It's like a fear 悪い夢の様で
It's like a fear, like a bad dream
目覚めても All I've got is bones
Even when I wake up, all I've got is bones
I'm in a panic? Get out, hurry
Oh, there're mysteries and miseries
Oh, there are mysteries and miseries
Dead or alive 狭間に揺られて
Dead or alive, swaying in the interstice
彷徨えば Right to left to hell
If I wander, right to left to hell
孤独の招待 感情の消滅
Lonely invitation, fading of emotions
踊る 1,2,3 steps on this dark stage
Dancing 1, 2, 3 steps on this dark stage
Raise your flag, march on, fight
仮面の淵へ 手を掛けどただ骨が鳴るのみ
Reaching for the edge of the mask, only bones are sounding
Wars and swords, tears and blood
溢る力が 不意に喰い出した
The overflowing power suddenly started to sneer
現実は何処へ 探して
Where is the truth? Seek it out
Where's my soul? Where's my heart?
現実に呑まれてく
Swallowed by reality
Don't hesitate, go this way
理解(わか)らない 構わない
I don't understand, I don't care
紛い力(もの)振るっても
Even if I wield a counterfeit power
ただこの世界を生き抜けよ
Just survive through this world
鳴呼 失くした哀しみがまた疼いてく...
Ah, the lost sadness throbs once again...
Misery-World
漆黒の空冷たく Midnight
Pitch black sky, cold midnight
夜の闇は Always drive me mad
The darkness of the night always drives me mad
Where is that star now? I found the star now
But it's so beautiful, I'm so doubtful
戸惑いの中 yadoru desire
Desire dwelling amidst bewilderment
見渡せば Sky and land and sea
If I look around, sky and land and sea
覇王の誘い 絶海の支配
Invitation of the overlord, domination of the abyss
登れ 1,2,3 steps to the royal throne
Climb, 1, 2, 3 steps to the royal throne
Cast a spell, call them up 絶望を呼べ
Cast a spell, call them up, summon despair
虚しさに酔い兵達が舞う
Soldiers dance, drunk on emptiness
Shouts and barks, grief and death
翳る者に 無慈悲を振るい下ろせ
Bring down ruthlessness upon those who sing
無情を行け 暴いて
Go with cruelty, uncover it
Break it all, take it all
手に入れろすべてを
Get your hands on everything
I just pray, or just play?
そうじゃない とまらない
That's not it, I can't stop
消えない疑念抱いて
Holding onto unceasing doubts
失くしたものをとり戻せよ
Reclaim what you have lost
ああ それさえ覆う狂気にまみれても
Ah, even if covered in madness that shrouds all else
Crazy World
見えない心と 確実にあるカラダ
With an invisible heart and a body that surely exists
信じたいものを上手に誓え
Pledge what you want to believe upon yourself
答えを捨てて走れ
Throw away the answer and run
Where's my soul? Where's my heart?
その意図を信じて
Believe in that will
Don't hesitate, go this way
理解(わか)らない 構わない
I don't understand, I don't care
夢でも現実(リアル)でも
Whether in a dream or reality
ただこの世界を生き抜けよ
Let's just survive through this world
さあどこまでも この足が行く限り
Now, as long as these feet will take me anywhere
Misery-World
真実は何処へ 探して
Where is the truth? Seek it out
Where's my soul?
It's like a fear 悪い夢の様で
It's like a fear, like a bad dream
目覚めても All I've got is bones
Even when I wake up, all I've got is bones
I'm in a panic? Get out, hurry
Oh, there're mysteries and miseries
Oh, there are mysteries and miseries
Dead or alive 狭間に揺られて
Dead or alive, swaying in the interstice
彷徨えば Right to left to hell
If I wander, right to left to hell
孤独の招待 感情の消滅
Lonely invitation, fading of emotions
踊る 1,2,3 steps on this dark stage
Dancing 1, 2, 3 steps on this dark stage
Raise your flag, march on, fight
仮面の淵へ 手を掛けどただ骨が鳴るのみ
Reaching for the edge of the mask, only bones are sounding
Wars and swords, tears and blood
溢る力が 不意に喰い出した
The overflowing power suddenly started to sneer
真実は何処へ 探して
Where is the truth? Seek it out
Where's my soul? Where's my heart?
現実に呑まれてく
Swallowed by reality
Don't hesitate, go this way
理解(わか)らない 構わない
I don't understand, I don't care
紛い力(もの)振るっても
Even if I wield a counterfeit power
ただこの世界を生き抜けよ
Just survive through this world
鳴呼 失くした哀しみがまた疼いてく...
Ah, the lost sadness throbs once again...
Misery-World
漆黒の空冷たく Midnight
Pitch black sky, cold midnight
夜の闇は Always drive me mad
The darkness of the night always drives me mad
Where is that star now? I found the star now
But it's so beautiful, I'm so doubtful
戸惑いの中 yadoru desire
Desire dwelling amidst bewilderment
見渡せば Sky and land and sea
If I look around, sky and land and sea
覇王の誘い 絶海の支配
Invitation of the overlord, domination of the abyss
登れ 1,2,3 steps to the royal throne
Climb, 1, 2, 3 steps to the royal throne
Cast a spell, call them up 絶望を呼べ
Cast a spell, call them up, summon despair
虚しさに酔い兵達が舞う
Soldiers dance, drunk on emptiness
Shouts and barks, grief and death
翳る者に 無慈悲を振るい下ろせ
Bring down ruthlessness upon those who sing
無情を行け 暴いて
Go with cruelty, uncover it
Break it all, take it all
手に入れろすべてを
Get your hands on everything
I just pray, or just play?
そうじゃない とまらない
That's not it, I can't stop
消えない疑念抱いて
Holding onto unceasing doubts
失くしたものをとり戻せよ
Reclaim what you have lost
ああ それさえ覆う狂気にまみれても
Ah, even if covered in madness that shrouds all else
Crazy World
見えない心と 確実にあるカラダ
With an invisible heart and a body that surely exists
信じたいものを上手に誓え
Pledge what you want to believe upon yourself
答えを捨てて走れ
Throw away the answer and run
Where's my soul? Where's my heart?
その意図を信じて
Believe in that will
Don't hesitate, go this way
理解(わか)らない 構わない
I don't understand, I don't care
夢でも現実(リアル)でも
Whether in a dream or reality
ただこの世界を生き抜けよ
Let's just survive through this world
Break it all...
手に入れろ 全てを
Get everything into your hands!
I just pray, or just play?
そうじゃない 止まらない 消えない疑念抱いて
That's not it, it won't stop, holding un-fading doubts
失くした物を取り戻せよ
Win back what you've lost!
嗚呼 それさえ覆う 狂気に染まれても Crazy world
Ah, even if covered in madness that veils all that, Crazy world
見えない心と 確かに在る身体
An invisible heart and a body that definitely exists
信じたいものを 己に誓え 何処へでも…
Swear to yourself what you want to believe, wherever...
真実を捨てて 走れ
Abandon the truth and run!
Where's my soul? Where's my heart?
その意志を信じて Don't hesitate, go this way
Believe in that will, Don't hesitate, go this way
理解らない 構わない 夢でも現実でも
I don't understand, I don't care, whether in dream or reality
ただこの世界を生き抜こう
Just survive through this world
さあ 何処まででも この足が行く限り Misery-World
Now, as far as these feet can go, Misery-World
Get get it up, get get get it up
聴き飽きた現実からの逃避
Escape from the reality I'm tired of hearing
だいたいはエゴの思想 永久なんてさ
Mostly egoistic thoughts, eternity, well
願ってもない 叶いやしない愛しないさ Holly
I don't wish for riches, I won't get them, Holly
聖なる夜の心地は非常に残酷な問答自問
The feeling of a holy night is a cruel internal debate
幸か不幸かは自分の眼にしか見えないさ No one gets close to me
Whether it's good or bad, visible only to your own eyes, No one gets close to me
Black memory どうなったっていい まだわからない世界で
Black memory, no matter what, in a world I still don't know,
滲む oh oh oh 叫ぶ
bleeding, oh oh oh, screaming
どうなったっていいから 僕を壊さないで
No matter what, don't break me,
覚めせ oh oh oh 限界突破見せてさ
wake up, oh oh oh, show me a breakthrough!
Get get it up, get get get it up
Like a loser いつだって満たされないよ きっとその方が強いから
Like a loser, never satisfied, surely because that way is stronger
迷宮なんてさ 出口もないし終わりもないさ Oh shit!!
A maze with no exit and no end, Oh shit!!
世の中に溢れ出す 異常に価値のない有象無象 関係ないけど あなたの心で
Overflowing into the world, abnormal, worthless masses, doesn't matter, but in your heart...
Black memory どうなったっていい まだわからない世界で
Black memory, no matter what, in a world I still don't know,
滲む oh oh oh 叫ぶ
bleeding, oh oh oh, screaming
どうなったっていいから 僕を壊さないで
No matter what, don't break me,
覚めせ oh oh oh 限界突破見せてやるさ
wake up, oh oh oh, I'll show you a breakthrough!
Get get it up, get get get it up
一瞬の迷いも見せない 僕の瞳が派手に落とすのは
Not showing a single moment of hesitation, what my eyes drop flashily...
一瞬の迷いも見せない
Showing not a single moment of hesitation,
僕の瞳が派手に落とすのは
what my eyes cast down so flashily
崩壊と希望の二層を既に離した
are already separate layers of collapse and hope—
記憶ただ…
just memories...
black memory
人生は守るべきモノで出来ていて
Life is made of things to protect,
いつか oh oh oh 超える
someday, oh oh oh, I'll surpass it.
どうなったっていい
No matter what happens,
とがめも言わせないよ
I won't let you blame me.
響け oh oh oh
Resound, oh oh oh,
全身全霊かけてやるさ
I'll give it my all with body and soul!
Happy birthday, Kobo!
silly bakka, silly ba, シリアスな shit, lemme shake it up
Silly bakka, silly ba, serious shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, gotta reckon ya
got a thirst for the worst looking, 馬鹿な cheap-ass
Got a thirst for the worst, looking like a cheap-ass
silly bakka, silly ba, silly ass-looking shit, gotta shake it up
wanna be lookin’ freaks, all they do is talk, getcha head out ya ass like what you got, huh?
Wanna be lookin' freaks, all they do is talk, getcha head out ya ass like what you got, huh?
毎度毎度神頼み (uh lalala)
Every single time, praying to the gods (uh, la-la)
免罪せんわそんな奴に (許し乞うたら?)
No absolution for a guy like that (you want forgiveness?)
あー、もう情状酌量の余地なし 即死刑、はい！ 地獄までお行きなさい！
Ah, no room for mitigating circumstances anymore—instant death, yes! Go to hell!
今すぐにお行きなさい
Go to hell right now!
メラメラ burning all day 真夏の楽園
Burning, burning all day, a midsummer paradise
メラメラ焼かれて灰になるまで
Burning, burning with jealousy until you turn to ashes
メロメロにさせて さあ踊り狂っちゃって
Make me fall head over heels, come on, dance like crazy
火炙りパラダイス go up and down
Barbecue paradise, go up and down
silly bakka, silly ba, シリアスな shit, lemme shake it up
Silly bakka, silly ba, serious shit, lemme shake it up
do what i want, shit, you know what i got, might be the pinnacle of cynical
and may i just remind you, act a fool, death's gotta fine you
c-a-double l, you already know scythe at the ready, slow and steady
C-A-double-L, you already know, scythe at the ready, slow and steady
give 'em a show, they wanna get real close, can't learn to let go
try 'n' dance with her, answer to, look out below
slaying to the beat, paint the street redder than rose
and slam 'em back 'til the sun rise and heaven's closed, sleep in 'til the next night
y'all know where we go, believe I still keep the tight shinigami flow, alright?
メラメラ burning all day 真夏の楽園
Burning, burning all day, a midsummer paradise
メラメラ焼かれて灰になるまで
Burning, burning with jealousy until you turn to ashes
メロメロにさせて、あー、冥土の土産に舞い上がれ、ほらまだまだ足りない
Make me fall head over heels, dancing as a parting gift from the underworld, it's still not enough!
spent all day beneath the sun, sun, sun, sun, sub is blasting out, dan-dan-dan-dan
i don't care, sing out, la-la-la-la, one night this time, you don't gotta run, run
愛は痛いもんだしさ 苦しくない 苦しくない
Love is a painful thing, there's no suffering, no suffering
灼熱に飛び込んで give it to ya, give it to ya
Jump into the scorching heat, give it to ya, give it to ya
み~みなさん！ You got the rest, Mori and Kobo's in the building so you know you're already dead!
Everyone! You got the rest, Mori and Kobo's in the building so you know you're already dead!
地獄までお行きなさい！
Go to hell!
メラメラ burning all day 真夏の楽園
Burning, burning all day, a midsummer paradise
メラメラ焼かれて灰になるまで
Burning, burning with jealousy until you turn to ashes
メロメロにさせて さあ踊り狂っちゃって
Make me fall head over heels, come on, dance like crazy
火炙りパラダイス go up and down
Barbecue paradise, go up and down
Bokobokobokobokoboko Kobo!
Kobo, thank you so much for singing with me! Yay! Thank you as well!
Kobo, wish you a happy birthday! Best birthday!
Yeah, you know, you you spit some flames. You're you're a great rap— actually Kobo, you should do more rap I think.
Yeah, you know, you spit some flames. You're a great rap— actually Kobo, you should do more rap I think.
Oh yeah, it was so difficult, but ah, Kobo is a pro rapper and yeah, you know...
We are one blood, right? Yeah, daddy? Yeah, singing together with you was awesome!
Awesome!
You nailed it! That was great.
Wow, すごい！素敵な後輩！You're amazing.
Wow, amazing! Such a wonderful junior! You're amazing.
Maybe follow in Mori's footsteps a little bit? I don't know.
Release the Kobo mixtape! Start the Kobo soundcloud!
Yeah, daddy, daddy. Since I'm here, let's take a picture.
Okay, let's make a cool pose first, okay?
Okay, picture time! Let's go! Yeah!
You kids these days, you're always taking photos and your hashtags...
Speaking of hashtag, hey, take a screenshot of us, and then make sure that you use the hashtag as the one time where I won't feel embarrassed if you spam my hashtag on Twitter/X, so please do it!
Speaking of hashtags, hey, take a screenshot of us, and make sure you use the hashtag as the one time I won't feel embarrassed if you spam my hashtag on Twitter/X, so please do it!
Strike a pose. Cheese! Yeah!
Get fancy with it.
Blue and pink is the best combination. What do you think? I think we look pretty good together.
Okay, looks good, right? Ah, one more daddy, cute pose, okay?
Say, say uwu, okay, daddy? Yeah, yeah, uwu, uwu right there, okay?
Okay, let's go. Cute pose!
Uwuuu!
Okay, looks good, right? Thanks again daddy for inviting me!
Ah, Kobo wants to go to the mall with mommy, okay? Bye bye!
Ah, Kobo wants to go to the mall with Mommy, okay? Bye-bye!
Ta-da! See you later Kobo! Bye-bye, thanks again!
Oh wait, no-downtime! No-downtime, no-downtime, no-downtime, hold on. Okay, no-downtime, we keep it moving, we keep it moving onto the next.
I'm gonna die.
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
ランドリー 今日はガラ空きでラッキーデイ
Laundry is wide open today, what a lucky day
かったりい油汚れもこれでバイバイ
Say goodbye to stubborn grease stains with this!
誰だ 誰だ 頭の中 呼びかける声は
Who is it, who is it calling out inside my head?
あれが欲しいこれが欲しいと歌っている
Singing about wanting that, wanting this
幸せになりたい 楽して生きていたい
I want to be happy, I want to live in ease
この手に掴みたい あなたのその胸の中
I want to grasp it in this hand, deep inside your chest
ハッピーで埋め尽くして レストインピースまで行こうぜ
Fill it all with happiness, let's go all the way to rest in peace
いつか見た地獄もいいところ 愛をばらまいて
The hell I once saw is actually not bad, scattering love all around
アイラブユー貶してくれ 全部奪って笑ってくれマイハニー
I love you, disparage me, take everything and laugh, my honey
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
なんか忘れちゃってんだ
I feel like I've forgotten something
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
4443で外れる炭酸水
Carbonated water popping open at 4443
ハングリー拗らせて吐きそうな人生
A life making me want to puke from pent-up hunger
「やまない雨はない」より先にその傘をくれよ
Before telling me "there's no rain that won't stop," give me that umbrella
あれが欲しいこれが欲しい全て欲しいただ虚しい
I want that, I want this, I want everything, yet I feel so empty
幸せになりたい 楽して生きていたい
I want to be happy, I want to live in ease
この手に掴みたい あなたのその胸の中
I want to grasp it in this hand, deep inside your chest
全部滅茶苦茶にしたい 何もかも消し去りたい
I want to mess everything up completely, erase it all
あなたのその胸の中
Deep inside your chest
ハッピーで埋め尽くして レストインピースまで行こうぜ
Fill it all with happiness, let's go all the way to rest in peace
良い子だけ迎える天国じゃどうも生きらんない
I just can't seem to live in a heaven that only welcomes good kids
アイラブユー貶して 奪って 笑ってくれマイハニー
I love you, disparage me, take it all, and laugh, my honey
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
なんか忘れちゃってんだ
I feel like I've forgotten something
ハッピー ラッキー こんにちはベイビィ
Happy, lucky, hello baby
良い子でいたい そりゃつまらない
Wanting to be a good kid? That's so boring
ハッピー ラッキー こんにちはベイビィソースイート
Happy, lucky, hello baby, so sweet
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
なんかすごい良い感じ
It feels strangely amazing
努力 未来 A BEAUTIFUL STAR
Effort, future, a beautiful star
しょっぺえな 初めて嗅いで舐めた出会いじょっぱいて
How salty. The first time I smelled and tasted our encounter,
平均的な正論が貧乏揺すり
Standard orthodox arguments cause fidgety tremors.
いらっしゃいませ ニンニク増しで混ぜて健康体
Welcome, mix it with extra garlic for a healthy body,
腹歌満たしている
filling my belly with song.
無茶なフリして突っおちゃった、きゃっターンです
Making reckless demands and diving right in, oops!
現状把握さ、から中段中もう
Grasping the current situation, stopping mid-way,
見せびらかし合いましょ、えっとかも？
Let's show off to each other, something like that?
変えられないして
Can't change it,
わかってるから直感で
Because I know, acting on pure intuition—
自己中な理解不能プレイヤーもっと
Selfish, incomprehensible player, more!
求められたなら惨敗か
If you asked for it, is it a crushing defeat?
くだらん口喧嘩でマシなんだ
It's better than a stupid verbal quarrel.
もっと もっと もう一回断るのに
More, more, to refuse one more time—
うざいくらい叫だって食らってだって譲れない日々よ
Screaming and taking blows, days I won't yield,
栄養になってまた汚し合え
Turning into nourishment, let's soil each other again.
脊髄反射の濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice of spinal reflex, I'm grateful.
試したいの、あたたかくて
I want to test it, being warm,
絶体絶命 夜は気持ちいい
Desperate situation, the night feels good.
平凡な生活 夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but—
先手必勝が気持ちいいな
Striking first feels so good.
帰ってすぐに水やり 人間の営み
Returning straight to watering plants, human activities.
実のところ恵まれても 虚無感が友達
Even if I'm actually blessed, emptiness is my friend.
眠気覚まし耳打ち 飲み干すまで合図汁
Whispering to wake up, signal juice until it's drunk dry.
仲良し ご要望じゃ
Good friends, as requested!
直感で 自己中な 理解不能
Intuitive, selfish, incomprehensible...
プレイヤーもっと 求められたなら
Player, more! If you asked for it,
惨敗か くだらん
is it a crushing defeat? How trivial.
細かいご指摘も有り難いが結局どこ
Detailed criticism is appreciated, but where in the end
開き直るのに
do I turn shameless?
うざいくらい叫だって食らってだって譲れない日々よ
Screaming and taking blows, days I won't yield,
栄養になってまた汚し合え
Turning into nourishment, let's soil each other again.
脊髄反射の濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice of spinal reflex, I'm grateful.
試したいの、あたたかくて
I want to test it, being warm,
絶体絶命 夜は気持ちいい
Desperate situation, the night feels good.
平凡な生活 夢見たけど
I dreamed of an ordinary life, but—
先手必勝が気持ちいいな
Striking first feels so good.
ただ穏やかでいたい 誰にも迷惑
I just want to be peaceful, without causing trouble
かけたぐはないと思うが 叩かれないと
to anyone, though I think that, but without being beaten,
戦わないと もらえない
without fighting, I can't receive anything.
単純明快でした
It was simple and clear.
うざいくらい叫だって食らってだって譲れない日々よ
Screaming and taking blows, days I won't yield,
栄養になってまた汚し合え
Turning into nourishment, let's soil each other again.
脊髄反射の濁った声で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a muddy voice of spinal reflex, I'm grateful.
言いたいことジャンケンで勝つ
Winning rock-paper-scissors for what I want to say—
まずは理官（理感）くまでこすり合え
First, rubbing together until sensory understanding is reached,
すぐ吐けなくて呆気なくて脊髄反射は
Unable to vomit it out right away, so anticlimactically, spinal reflex
歪んだ脳で歌えば感謝です
If I sing with a distorted brain, I'm grateful.
だいじ、痒いし、うっせえ、だいだい
It's important, it itches, it's annoying, generally—
くだらないことで笑いたかった
I wanted to laugh about stupid things.
満たされない不満感暴れるの移る
Unsatisfied dissatisfaction, rampaging infection,
でも憤れない傷にはセッションで健康で気持ちいいな
But un-resentful wounds, with session and health, it feels good.
Yay! Thank you so much, everybody! That was Zanki, Time Left.
Speaking of time left, there is none. There's no time left!
But, uh, this has been a really, really amazing NODOWNTIME live show with you guys and all of the amazing guests that came here.
So thank you so much for coming to support me and have a great live show.
My fourth one. Wow, my fourth, my fourth birthday here in Hololive, and I'm so, so happy to have gotten this chance to celebrate it with you here in the underworld!
It was fantastic. But, you know, it is my birthday,
and when it comes to birthdays, there's there's something important to announce.
What does everybody announce during their birthday? Um, hold on, I'm thinking. I don't know, I forgot. I forgot.
Wait, it's I remember, I remember. I remember. Sorry, I beat some a little scatterbrained, I'm sorry. It's because I'm excited.
Birthday goods, tada!
Birthday Celebration 2024
everybody!
This, this is definitely a set that I'm super excited to introduce to you guys.
By the way, check it out me playing the bass.
Hey, it's not a lie.
Because for my birthday, I bought myself a bass!
Yay, I'm going to start learning again.
I'm not a fake bass player, stop.
Don't call me that, I'm not a fake bass player.
Boko boko ni suru zo. Beat you up, okay?
It's cool. The illustration is cool.
Shokai shimasu ne! Next!
So, first of all, first and foremost, Eternal Rest Square Cushion.
Would you like to sleep forever, Dead Beats?
Well, good news for you, I have a cushion that is extremely comfy and super special.
You're going to fall asleep immediately if you use this cushion, but I can't guarantee that because I think there's like some legal stuff.
Check it out, the art is beautiful, it's high quality and amazing.
I think it's high quality.
I hope that you enjoy it, and you can take lots of naps with it.
I wish I could take naps.
Next, next slide is... Hey, Dead Beats.
Do you guys like fashion?
I like fashion, do you like fashion?
There are a lot of designer brands in the human world that I can't name right now because also legal things.
However, in the underworld, we kind of have our own designer brands as well.
And I have collaborated with one of my favorites to create this Underworldian Designer Muffler.
Yeah, I kind of consider this like the Riz pack, birthday, birthday goods.
Check it out, Calliope Mori symbol.
You can find other Dead Beats out in the wild without just having Mori on your shirt, you know?
It's very convenient.
And the tag is also super cute, so make sure that you get nice and warm and snug for fall and winter.
I hope you guys enjoy wearing this and adding it to your wardrobe.
Next slide, please.
Additionally, we have Dead Beat Honorary Ring.
I know you guys will be excited about this one.
But do not get it twisted, this is not a marriage ring. Kekkon shitenai yo, Dead Beats.
I'm not going to marry you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm too busy.
I'm too busy, but, but if you like, you could go ahead and purchase this Dead Beat Honorary Ring.
So that you can also find other Dead Beats out in the wild.
It makes it a little bit easier, right?
And plus, if it doesn't fit on your finger, your fingers may be too big or too small, you can go ahead and put it on a necklace.
And it's still very, very fashionable.
I really love the design, it reminds me of you guys.
So, I hope that you guys will enjoy wearing this very special ring.
And next, last, we have the "Your Last Shot" Glass Set of shot glasses.
Go find a Dead Beat and cheers them.
And drink some alcohol that reminds you of Mori, or maybe even Mori alcohol, I don't know.
Um, but they're they're very cute.
It's a cute set with some Mori designs on them, and I want to see them at every Dead Beat birthday party.
Um every Dead Beat party in general, I hope that you guys use these a lot.
Um to to go wild and party.
No downtime. Whoo!
Um, I guess that's about it.
Next slide, please.
Um, we also have a situation voice. It's called Backstage with Calliope.
I don't know what this one sounds like because it hasn't happened yet.
But maybe if I see you after the show, oh, I might remember it. I don't know.
Maybe because it's yet to happen.
Also, if you get the full set, you get a super secret special special one that's included in there, which is pretty neat.
So, please look forward to that.
And next slide.
For the entire full set, um if you buy the whole thing, you will get a signed card by me.
Mori Calliope.
And I'm signing all of them.
T'm signing every single card because you guys are great and I want everybody to get a chance
I'm signing every single card because you guys are great and I want everybody to get a chance
to get Mori's signature.
I've been making it really easy for you guys recently to be honest, between all the things I've been signing, but, but this one I definitely...
I definitely will be signing just for you.
As many of you guys that buy the full set, you will get a handsigned postcard from me.
So, yeah, please look forward to it.
And next slide, please.
Uh here's the full set, here's everything that you get with it.
And the cart will open as soon as the live stream is over or on the hour.
Uh so make sure that that you check it out. Uh make sure that you're I guess you don't really need to be fast.
Because I'm signing every single one, but make sure that you grab yours today.
No downtime. Whoo!
So that is the that's the merch situation.
Um those are the goods, my birthday goods.
I'm very happy with them.
I can't wait to receive mine, and I hope that you guys look forward to getting yours.
Now,
we do have something else that I want to show you, a very special PV
that I think maybe some of you guys have already seen, I don't know.
But it's about something, it's about something really, really awesome.
And I'm very excited about it.
So let's watch it.
PV,
dozo.
we do have something else that I want to show you, a very special PV
that I think maybe some of you guys have already seen, I don't know.
But it's about something, it's about something really, really awesome.
And I'm very excited about it.
So let's watch it.
PV,
dozo.
ハーレイ・クインか
Harley Quinn...
ゴッサム・シティの犯罪王、ジョーカーのパートナー
Accomplice to The Joker,
known as the Gotham City's Clown Prince of Crime
完璧じゃない、プリンちゃん！
Oh that's perfect, Puddín'!
こんなのは長い長いのショーの導入だ。
This is just a long introduction to the show.
今の世界は醜く…何より不公平だ。
The world we know is so hideous and...
above of all, unfair.
ゲートに繋がる世界
A world connected by the "Gate"
あなたたち5人には、ある任務について貰う。
The Super-Villains are sent to ISEKAI
任務？
A mission?
平和のための任務だ。
A peace-keeping mission.
平和？俺たちが？
Us? Peace?
キャスティングを誤ったな。
They've made casting errors for sure.
最強！
Take that!
バカでやがる
She's nuts
俺、頑張る。
Do my best, me.
我々王国と帝国の戦争は、すでに数十年におよんでいる。
The war between our kingdom and the Empire
has been going on for decades.
どうすればこの軍勢を止められる？
How do we defeat their troops?
俺たちが打って出れば、瞬く間に平和になる！
If we go out and fight,
there will be peace in an instant!
この方たちを信じてみてもよいのではないかと。
I think we should trust them.
何？ちらちら見てたよね、私じゃなかった
Hey, you were eyeing me earlier
とにかく今はこの国と友好関係を結ぶことが先決だ。
We need to establish a friendly relationship
with them first.
この戦争を終わらせようではないか！
Let us put an end to this war!
一まずは憂さ晴らしに警報のやつをぶっ潰す。
I will knock 'em out to blow off steam.
じゃあ、始めちゃう？
So, shall we kick it off?
Yeah, that's karma
yeah, get down
checkmate, i'm a superstar
stay insane, but you rock with it
yeah, like 24/7, i'm a hot mess ya, love-hate
Yeah, like 24/7, I'm a hot mess, love-hate
get less boring, oh, my god
ホームラン、バタバタ swing my shot, ah
Home run, batabata swing my shot, ah
whoop-whoop, uh, yeah, like a villainous
villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains don't change
派手にブチかまそう
Let's make a flashy blow
Don't worry, puddin'
I will come back to you...
Yeeh everybody, wow!
So, I have been chosen to sing the ending theme for the TV anime Suicide Squad ISEKAI, to air from July.
So, I have been chosen to sing the ending theme
for the TV anime Suicide Squad ISEKAI, to air from July.
I'm so excited about this, I waited so long to tell you guys about it, and...
I'm so excited about this, I waited so long
to tell you guys about it, and...
And I know I already did tell you about it, but even saying it now it feels like a, like a dream.
And I know I already did tell you about it,
but even saying it now it feels like a dream.
I mean, even, even when I joined Holo, I said in my, my debut one of my goals was, was to make a song for anime, but really it's been my lifelong goal to do something like that and...
I mean, even when I joined Holo, I said in my debut
one of my goals was to make a song for anime,
but really it's been my lifelong goal...
I've, I've already cried a lot over this. I'm not going to here, but I'm very emotional about it.
I've already cried a lot over this.
I'm not going to here, but I'm very emotional about it.
So please look forward to it. Um, the, the animation production is by the amazing WIT Studio.
So please look forward to it.
Um, the animation production is by the amazing WIT Studio.
So you know it's going to be a banger. Um, it's incredible. And, I really want everybody to watch it when it comes out.
So you know it's going to be a banger. It's incredible.
And I really want everybody to watch it when it comes out.
So please make sure that you stay tuned when it does air. And there's still something else I'd like to show you.
So please make sure that you stay tuned when it does air.
And there's still something else I'd like to show you.
A bit of a teaser of sorts? I don't know. But let's see what else Mori has cookin'. PV,どうぞ!
A bit of a teaser of sorts? I don't know.
But let's see what else Mori has cookin'. PV,どうぞ!
2024.04.25
NEW SONG RELEASE
WITH
COMING SOON
Whoa! What was that? Haha! What was that? Hmm?
New song, but what kind of new song? I don't know, is there, is there are there any guesses in the chat? What could this be?
New song, but what kind of new song?
I don't know, are there any guesses in the chat?
Well, we don't really have a lot of details about it yet, but it's a secret for another time.
Well, we don't really have a lot of details about it yet,
but it's a secret for another time.
So please keep your eyes peeled for the big reveal coming sometime soon, I'm sure. Look forward to it.
So please keep your eyes peeled for the big reveal
coming sometime soon, I'm sure. Look forward to it.
Now, that's it for the announcements. However, however, there is, uh there's still one song left.
Now, that's it for the announcements.
However, there is still one song left.
That's right, because this train doesn't stop moving, no downtime, baby. I'm starting to feel it. I'm starting to feel it, but perfect timing.
That's right, because this train doesn't stop moving,
no downtime, baby. I'm starting to feel it.
Um, I'm going to change clothes. So don't watch me, stay there. Look over there!
Um, I'm going to change clothes.
So don't watch me, stay there. Look over there!
Please don't watch a lady change. Whoa! That was fast.
Uh, Calli's very fast. Check it. It's my Reaper Reaper t-shirts. I have a bunch of different designs. You can choose your color and stuff like that.
Uh, Calli's very fast. Check it.
It's my Reaper Reaper t-shirts. I have a bunch of designs.
They're on the Mori store. Make sure that you grab yours if you haven't already. It's very neat. Check it out. I'm very, very proud of this one.
They're on the Mori store. Make sure that you grab yours
if you haven't already. It's very neat. Check it out.
This one in particular I drew myself, so it's very special to me. Now, let's do this last song you guys, a song that I've wanted to perform since my early days in HoloEN, I think you guys will understand why...
This one in particular I drew myself,
so it's very special to me. Now, let's do this last song,
a song that I've wanted to perform since HoloEN.
I think you guys will understand why it's so special when you see it. Everybody, thank you for coming. Let's rock!
I think you guys will understand why it's so special
when you see it. Everybody, thank you for coming. Let's rock!
さあ 眠眠打破
Come on, get up and wake up
昼夜逆転
Day and night reversed
VOX AC 30W
VOX AC 30 watts
テレキャスター背負ったサブカルボーイがバンド仲間にやっほー
A suburban boy with a telecaster on his back says hi
アルバイトはネクラモード
Part-time job mode is gloomy
Hey, rise and shine, folks,
don't let a rated clock drag you down, fuck sakes,
AC30 watt, crank it up,
second hand telecaster, pass it to the bass with the boys in the band, say yahoo!
second-hand telecaster, pass it to the bass with the boys in the band, say yahoo!
So, chocolate psychics slow down,
AT field's on the bench, show down,
wanna play like a shining star, look soon, and the gods can't hide forever, boy!
Listen well, guys and gals,
mind your fortune, talents you can't fence around,
they'll just tire you down, boys be ambitious...
...like this old man (that's right),
like this old man there,
hang you with the bangs, with the attitude,
who's the one that you follow, watch you can bound down to...
...down to,
down to!
Roki, roki, rock'n, rock'n, roll,
gotcha, get it twisted, you're the one that's taking control!
Rocking, rocking now, rocking, rocking, roll,
strumming that guitar to the rhythm that just won't stop, don't stop!
Let me see you let it out, rest in peace to any doubt!
Keep rocking, rocking now, rocking, rocking, roll!
All right, so hold up, like what's the plan?
Rate a first-rate string player, looking, no, you can't!
And the worst case hanging around, same shit, underground, got a rep, not a crown, so what?
Got something to say? You better say it loud,
you gotta whack out sound a little more profounded,
with your on and on, it goes on and on and on and on,
offs with opinions, not by a lost shot!
When you're hot, gotta take the heat,
so when you're burning both, because the streets demand you stay tough,
with the makeup glamour style, you can fake to a gangster a little while!
So, both be ambitious, like this old man,
cause you can't be starters, sing, make 'em real frosting, last no-fucking-five,
better take a selfie!
You ain't gonna die on me, we gotta stay alive!
Rocking, rocking now, rocking, rocking, roll,
even some some of love bringing emotion that just won't stop, don't stop,
she is the girl with my beloveds, tease her world and light it up by...
...rocking, rocking now, rocking, rocking, roll, rock it down!
Give it up for whole life English misfit band,
talking out Shiori on the keyboards, you know, internet starts drum,
ukulele and good dad, Amelia Watson, guitar,
Mori bitch, so you don't wanna have fastest,
playing to the masses,
Margaria her headset is in,
now we are past this,
Ayy, yo, with a pro medicine,
give me, give me that impression,
and apprehension keeps stressing, depressing,
leaving and I'm guessing under the weather,
disbelieves suspending, big sorry guys if I do apologize!
Baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby...
You ain't gonna die on me, we gotta stay alive!
Rocking, rocking now, rocking, rocking, roll,
strumming that guitar to the rhythm that just won't stop, don't stop!
Let me see you let it out, rest in peace to any doubt!
Keep rocking, rocking now, rocking, rocking, roll!
Proving I won't die here,
you ain't dying either,
music rocking fire,
it's how we stay alive!
Hell, yeah, thank you everyone!
Miss fucking roki!
Rap and rock and roll!